# Branden Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

github.com/BrandenDaniel 🖸

**J** 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fiery passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautifully spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I have crafted outstanding websites that have wowed clients and peers, boasting professionally structured and understandable code. I am currently learning React. is and API integrations.

### **Work Experience**

#### LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present

Melbourne CBD, VIC / Hybrid

Front-end Web Developer

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients and governments across Australia.

- · Maintained proprietary leasing/salary packaging software with clean & structured front-end code. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Maintain and managed of all LeasePLUS's websites/portals (i.e. SalaryPackagingPLUS, LeasePLUS)

#### LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer - salary deductions receivable & payable

Apr. 2022 — Sept. 2022 Melbourne CBD, VIC

.

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Melbourne CBD, VIC

North Laverton, VIC

Arcadian Digital &

Junior Front-end Web Developer

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian deliver tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes.

- Collaborative work with project managers/senior developers, producing smart and intuitive solutions
- · Build and structure WordPress reusable child themes
- · Build and maintan company's own WordPress plugins and themes

## Bebble Media *𝚱* May. 2018 − Jun. 2019

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their e-

commerce and online presence.

Junior Front-end Web Developer

- · Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

#### **Tech Stack & Skills** Interests & Hobbies JavaScript | React | HTML | CSS | Sass ETFs & Index Funds Personal Finance Tech jQuery | Bootstrap | Git | API integration Critically Acclaimed Films | Youtube Work **Personal Projects** MySalPack (employee portal) & 2023 My Web Portfolio & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | Sass | Blazor | Bootstrap React | JavaScript | HTML Sass MySalPack (employer portal) & 2022 YouTube Clone & 2023 JavaScript | | jQuery | | Sass | | Blazor Bootstrap React | Material UI | Rapid API Axios Sass Print Strategy Management & 2019 Cryptoverse & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | WordPress | Bootstrap | CSS Rapid API React | Redux | Axios Sass Ant Design

## **Education**

Udacity

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Oct. 2017 – May 2018

Online

Online

**Team Treehouse** 

May - Aug. 2017

Front End Web Development Track

Jul. 2016 — Apr. 2017

Melbourne, VIC

RMIT University

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology
Relevant Courses Included:

- Web Programming
- User-centered Design